ralphlauren.com.au 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy | Ralph Lauren

## Privacy Policy

Ralph Lauren Asia Pacific Limited and its affiliates (collectively, " Ralph Lauren") respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to personal information we collect (i) on this website, (ii) at Ralph Lauren stores, Ralph Lauren Factory Outlet Stores (collectively, the "Stores"), and (iii) through the other channels described below. Ralph Lauren is responsible for this website.

The Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect on this site, in our Stores, and in other ways discussed below, how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. The notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the personal information. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask us to (i) access, change or not use the personal information you have provided to us, (ii) withdraw any consent you previously provided to us, (iii) tell us to refrain from communicating with you about our products or services, and (iv) answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.

#### Information We Collect and How We Use It

Individuals may choose to provide personal information (such as name, contact details and payment information) through this website, in our Stores and through the other channels described below. Here are the ways you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit. We also tell you how we may use the information. Your provision of information is voluntary. However, if you choose not to provide information as requested, we may not be able to supply you with products or services as applicable.

### Our Website

#### Surveys, Sweepstakes and Promotions

On this website, you may be able to participate in surveys, sweepstakes and other promotions. If you choose to participate in these promotions, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address and telephone number. We use the information you provided to administer our contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. We also may use the information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions, but only if you have given us your consent to do so.

#### Electronic Newsletters

You may be able to sign up on this site to receive electronic newsletters and promotional emails from Ralph Lauren, including new ideas, special offers and event information. To sign up, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, age, gender, shopping preferences and email preferences. We use this information to send you communications about our products and services, invitations to specials sales and events at Stores located near you, and notices of new arrivals. We also use this information to tailor our newsletters to reflect your preferences. You can choose at any time not to receive marketing emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link within our marketing emails or by clicking here. There is no charge to you to unsubscribe.

#### Email to a Friend

You may be able to share certain content from this website with your friends. To send information to your friends, we ask for your friends' and your email addresses. We use this information only to fulfill your request. We do not retain the information you provide in connection with this feature, except to send the requested content. We will not include any other advertisements within the messages sent to your friends.

#### Contact Us

If you communicate with us through the "Contact Us" link on this site, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, post code and telephone number. We use this information to respond to and communicate with you about your questions and comments.

#### Other Site Features

We offer visitors to this website various features for their information and enjoyment, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal information so we can provide you with these features and send you communications about our products, services and promotions.

#### Information We Collect by Automated Means

We obtain certain information by automated means when you visit our website, such as the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors and understand what products and services you might prefer. We collect this information through various means, such as "cookies" and "web beacons."

#### Cookies

Like many companies, we use "cookies" on this website. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit certain websites. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. We use cookies, for example, to preserve the contents of your virtual shopping bag between visits. We also use cookies to measure activity on the site and determine which areas and features of the site are the most popular.

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie and how to disable existing cookies. Without cookies, however, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our site features.

#### Web Beacons

Certain pages on this website contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). Web beacons are used for internal purposes, such as to obtain the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, and the type of browser used to view the page. We also retain service providers who use web beacons to assess the effectiveness of our email communications and learn what pages our visitors viewed.

Our Stores 

Here are some of the ways we collect personal information in our Stores and a description of how we use the information:

#### Shopping

When you buy products or obtain services in our Stores, we ask you for information we need to process your purchase or provide you with the services you requested. Depending on the payment method you use, and as permitted by applicable law, we may ask for information such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, checking account information or payment card information. We also collect information about your purchase, such as the items you bought, the price of the items, the payment method you used and if the product was on sale. We use this information to process your transaction. We also collect your information that you provide to our staff (which may include communications with our staff, whether formally or informally), or which we otherwise collect from you or third parties. We will use the information for the purposes of marketing and promotion communications, customer research, analysis, after sales service, customer care and general administration. Your information may include, without limitation, identification, characteristics, family status, occupation, habits, interests, shopping preferences, and other information relating to and necessary for the purposes set forth above. 

#### Customer Registry

You may join our Customer Registry at our Stores. To join, we ask for your name, postal address, email address and mobile and home telephone numbers. You also may choose to provide us with your age and gender. We use this information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions and for other marketing and customer service purposes.

#### Customer Satisfaction Surveys

When you buy products or obtain services in our Stores, we may ask you to complete a customer satisfaction survey. If you choose to do so, you may provide information such as your name, email address, telephone number, age, gender and other demographic information, in addition to your comments. Providing any of this information is optional. We use the information you provide to improve our products and services, and enhance your shopping experience.

Use of Personal Information in Direct Marketing 

We intend to use information collected from you through this website, in our Stores and through the other channels described below, including your name, email address, postal address and contact number, gender and birth date to send you communications (including electronic newsletter and mobile marketing) on Ralph Lauren's fashion, accessories, shoes, leather goods, fragrance, sunglasses, jewelry, timepieces, home products and services. We may transfer your personal information to our group companies, affiliates and business partners who provide the same products and services for direct marketing purposes, including companies outside the jurisdiction your data was collected in. Your prior consent is required before we may use or disclose your personal information for direct marketing purposes. You may withdraw your consent any time by contacting us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below or by changing your email preferences in the “my account” feature of this website or by using any other unsubscribe facilities provided in our electronic marketing communications.

### Other Ways We Collect Personal Information

#### Customer Assistance

You may call our customer service line for information about our products or personal shopping advice. If you do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and, if you choose to make a purchase, your payment card information. We use this information to respond to your request and process your transaction.

#### Other Ways We Obtain and Use Information

In addition to the ways we collect information about you described above, we also may obtain information about you from third parties. We may use your personal information to provide you with products or services you request (such as tailoring services or merchandise returns), enhance your shopping experience and communicate with you about our products, services and promotions. In addition, we may use your personal information for internal purposes, such as fraud and theft prevention, accident reporting, development and administration of our sites and Stores, data analytics, and compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures.

#### Department Stores

Our products are available for sale in many department stores. Personal information collected in these department stores is not provided to Ralph Lauren. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of department stores in which our products are sold. Department stores may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review when you provide them with your personal information. We are not responsible for the department stores' personal information practices.

### Information We Share

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our customers, except as described here. We may share the personal information you provide to us with our group companies, affiliates worldwide, and business partners for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We also may share the information with our service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.

We also may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process (such as a court order), (ii) in response to a request by law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided to us in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy. Following such a sale or transfer, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your personal information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that information.

### Links to Other Sites

This website may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Ralph Lauren. Linked sites may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with Ralph Lauren, any use of those sites, or the privacy practices of those sites.

### How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect the personal information you provide on this website or in our Stores against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use and other unlawful forms of processing.

### Transfer of Personal Information to Other Countries

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which you originally provided it; these countries include but are not limited to Hong Kong and the United States. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Access and Correction

Subject to applicable law, we provide you with access to personal information we have retained about you and the ability to review, correct, update, block or delete the information where it is inaccurate. Subject to applicable law, we may limit or deny access to personal information where providing such access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances. Please submit your request to the address specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. Please include your name, email address and postal address in your request.

### Your Choices

We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you. You may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us or object at any time on legitimate grounds and free of charge to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward.

You can choose not to receive marketing communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our marketing emails or contacting us as specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. Please include your name, email address and postal address if you send us your request by email or postal mail.

You may ask us to refrain from sharing your information with certain of our affiliates and other third parties for their marketing purposes.

### Updates to Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices or relevant laws. We will post a prominent notice on the site to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the top of the notice when it was updated.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences or if you would like to make a complaint about the manner in which your personal information has been collected or handled by Ralph Lauren, please contact us as indicated below. Ralph Lauren will give due consideration and respond as appropriate to any question or complaint :

Ralph Lauren Asia Pacific Limited  
Attention: Customer Service Manager  
c/o 35/F, Tower 1,  
The Gateway, Harbour City,  
Tsim Sha Tsui,  
Hong Kong  
Email: [CustomerAssistance@RalphLauren.asia](mailto:CustomerAssistance@RalphLauren.asia)  
Tel: +852 2643 1400

July 19, 2016
